This
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): is a place of promise, a way of life and hope for the future. Here we harvest God's gifts from above and below. Here we give thanks for our blessings, celebrate our heritage, honor tradition. Here we salute the flag and honor those who fought for it. This is our land, our people, our Kentucky.
And
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): this is where Rand Paul lives, works, raises his family, and serves our community. From Bowling Green to Paducah, Glasgow to Lexington, Corbin and Louisville, Rand Paul has provided free eye surgery for uninsured patients, and Rand Paul restores the gift of sight to God's newest creation. Rand
Speaker 3: never forgot how sad it was for him to watch his grandmother lose her vision,
Speaker 4: and And I think that really
cemented
Speaker 4: in him, the desire to be an ophthalmologist. One of the most gratifying things for Rand in his career has been the ability to do eye surgery on children from Guatemala. Being a physician gives Rand a unique perspective in Washington, simply because he's trained to diagnose a problem and find a solution.
Speaker 5: Today, we need solutions more than ever to stop Washington and restore liberty.
Speaker 6: And one leader stands in Washington's way. One fighting the Washington machine. One who will never give up, no matter the cost. And
Speaker 7: one who stands for us. Rand
Paul.
I'll
Speaker 8: continue to advocate for balanced budgets. I'll continue to advocate and fight against president's
Speaker 9: war on coal, the president's war on Kentucky jobs.
Speaker 10: Rand Paul headlined a panel of people connected to the coal industry as part of a forum. I think
Speaker 11: the time for
Speaker 12: talk is over, the time is to resist the president. I will be a loud and vocal opponent of anybody he
Speaker 13: wants to appoint to the Supreme Court.
Speaker 14: Most people in Lexington, most people really in Kentucky want someone who will stand up against the president's policies. If you could have just one constitutional amendment, what would it be?
Term limits. Rand Paul is
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): standing with us. This is our country, built by our forefathers, not government. This is our home,
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): earned through effort, not entitlement.
Speaker 17 (lower-pitched voice): These are our freedoms, given to us by God, not man. And this is our champion.
Rand
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): Paul stands strong for the Kentucky we love. And Kentucky stands with Rand Paul because he defends our liberty. Stand for
Speaker 18: freedom. Stand for Kentucky. Stand with Rand. Rand Paul.
You